let questions = [
    {
        question: "What is the term used to describe the NCAAB tournament?",
        choices: ["April Angerness", "March Madness", "May Madness", "June Joyous"],
        correctAnswer: "March Madness",
    },
    {
        question: "Which school has the most national championships in college basketball?",
        choices: ["Duke", "Kentucky", "UCLA", "North Carolina"],
        correctAnswer: "UCLA",
    },
    {
        question: "Including play-in games, how many teams make the NCAAB tournament?",
        choices: ["68", "64", "60", "72"],
        correctAnswer: "68",
    },
    {
        question: "Which school did Michael Jordan play college basketball at?",
        choices: ["Michigan", "Duke", "Kentucky", "North Carolina"],
        correctAnswer: "North Carolina",
    },
    {
        question: "What was the nickame for Michigan's team during the 1991 NCAAB season?",
        choices: ["Fantastic Four", "Flawless Five", "Fab Five", "Fit Five"],
        correctAnswer: "Fab Five",
    },
    {
        question: "Which coach has the most wins in NCAAB history?",
        choices: ["Jim Boeheim", "Mike Krzyzewski", "Roy Williams", "Bob Knight"],
        correctAnswer: "Mike Krzyzewski",
    },
    {
        question: "Which coach had the iconic speech at the ESPY's stating 'don't give up, don't ever give up?'",
        choices: ["Jim Valvano", "Jim Boeheim", "Lou Carnasecca", "Mike Krzyzewski"],
        correctAnswer: "Jim Valvano",
    },
    {
        question: "Which former Duke player has the most points in school history?",
        choices: ["Christian Laettner", "Kyle Singler", "Jon Scheyer", "JJ Redick"],
        correctAnswer: "JJ Redick",
    },
    {
        question: "Who was the first 16 seed to beat a number 1 seed in the NCAAB tournament?",
        choices: ["Fairleigh Dickinson University", "University of Maryland, Baltimore County", "Florida Gulf Coast University", "Howard University"],
        correctAnswer: "University of Maryland, Baltimore County",
    },
    {
        question: "What was the lowest seed to ever win the NCAAB championship?",
        choices: ["8 seed", "6 seed", "10 seed", "12 seed"],
        correctAnswer: "8 seed",
    }
];